布雷迪神父在小教堂
Father Brady's in the chapel.
想叫他来就按呼叫按钮
Just push the call-button if you want to see him.
你上一次吃东西是什么时候
When was the last time you ate?
什么
What?
吃的  你最近吃东西了吗
Food. Have you eaten anything lately?
我没事
I'm fine.
来吧  查克  我们去诺维家吃点东西
Come on, Chuck. Let's go over to Novi's
活动活动  透下气  吃点三明治
and strech our legs, get some air, couple of hoagies.
你这个时候想吃三明治
You wanna get a sandwich now?
想想而已
Just a thought.
好吧
Alright.
你记不记得那次我不小心邀请了
Remember that time I accidentally invited
凯茜和谢丽尔参加妈妈的惊喜派对
Kathy and Cheryl to Mom's surprise party?
跳舞时有点尴尬
It was kind of tricky out on the dance floor.
那晚真有意思
It was a fun night.
我只记得全家人给你收拾烂摊子
I just remember the whole family cleaning up after you,
妈妈离开自己的生日派对
and Mom leaving her own birthday party
开车送人回家
drive one of them off.
说真的  查克  我们得吃东西
Seriously, Chuck, we gotta eat.
听着
It -- look.
让妈妈一个人待几分钟没问题的
Mom'll be okay for a few minutes.
都三天了  还可能再持续三天
It's been three days. It could be three more.
好吗
Okay?
走吧  哥们
Let's go, buddy.
吉米  你想吃东西就去吃
Jimmy, you want to eat, go eat.
我给你带点回来吧
I'll bring you something --
烤牛肉  不加番茄  意式配菜
um, roast beef, no tomato, Italian on the side.
好吗
All right?
马上回来
'Kay. Be right back.
妈
Mom?
吉米
Jimmy.
不  妈  是我  查克
No, Mom, it's me -- Chuck.
吉米
Jimmy.
不  妈  我是
No, Mom, it's m--
就这样了
So this is it, then?
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
她签过不抢救预嘱
She has that DNR.
你弟弟在这里吗
Is your brother in the building?
我们可以呼叫他来
We can use the intercom.
不用了
No.
查尔斯  你想让我们给谁打电话吗
Charles...is there anyone you want us to call?
查克
Chuck.
Hey, Chuck.
查克  妈妈呢  怎么了
Chuck, where's Mom? What happened?
她去世了
She's gone.
什么  什么时候
What? W-when?
她怎么
How did...
她醒过吗  她说什么了吗
Did she wake up? Did she say anything?
没有
No.
打911
Call 911.
快啊
Call 911!
欧尼  出去
Ernie, get out here!
你干什么
Hey, what the hell are you doin?!
明天再来
Come back tomorrow.
给你打五折
It'll be half the price.
需要救护车
Yeah, I need an ambulance.
-我这有纸巾  -好
- I got paper towels. - Good.
给我个垫子垫他的头
Some for his head, gimme a cushion for his head!
等下  先别挂
Um, yeah, hold on. Hold on one second.
查克  振作点
Chuck. Come on. Come on.
查克
Chuck.
-查克  听得见吗  -复印中心
- Hey, Chuck, with us, buddy? - The copy center.
-查克  -金街615号
- Chuck. - 615 Gold.
哥们  你没事吧
Buddy, y-you okay?
不  他脸色没有发青
No, he doesn't look blue.
-我们这就送你去医院  -兰斯
- We're gonna get you to the hospital, okay? - ‭Lance.
-会没事的  -我在这儿工作
- Everything will be all right. - I work here.
坚持一下  查尔斯  快到了
Hang tight, Charles. We're almost there.
小心
Watch yourself.
让一让
Coming through.
数三下  一二三
On 3. 1, 2, 3.
移床
Transferring.
查尔斯·麦吉尔  快六十岁了
This is Charles McGill, late 50s.
打印店雇员看见他在店内昏厥
He had a syncopal episode at a print shop, witnessed by an employee.
失去意识时间约一分钟
Estimated loss of consciousness was one minute.
生命体征平稳
His vitals are stable.
前额有裂伤
He's got a laceration on his forehead
应该需要缝合
that appears to need suturing.
查尔斯  你感觉如何
Charles, how you doing tonight?
能跟我说话吗
Can you talk to me?
有症状突然发作吗
Seizure activity?
运送途中没有  也没有报告
Not in transfer and none reported.
无尿失禁
No urinary incontinence.
有家属在场吗
Do we have any family members?
-他弟弟在等候室  -好
- There's a brother in the waiting room. - Okay.
你给他打多少点滴了
How much fluid did you give him?
这还是第一公升
That's the first liter.
-灯  -你说什么  查尔斯
- Lights. - ‭What's that, Charles?
把灯关掉
Mnh, you have to turn off the lights.
-现在不能关灯  亲爱的  -天啊
-No, we can't do that right now, sweetie. - Ohh! God.
你撞伤了头
You fell and hit your head.
我们得做一些检查  好吗
We're gonna need to do some tests, okay?
-不  不  -我们没办法...
- No. No. - ‭We can't --
我们需要开着灯才能帮你
We need the lights on to help you.
-不  -查尔斯  你能用力握我的手吗
- No. - ‭Charles, can you squeeze my hand really hard?
把灯关...
Turn the lights...
那是什么
What is that?
检查你的吸氧量而已  查尔斯
Okay, we're just checking your oxygen there, Charles.
-你有任何药物过敏吗  -没有
- Do you have any allergies? - No.
目前是否在服用任何药物
Are you on any medications?
没有
Ohh, no.
好的  我现在要动一动你的手和腿
Okay. I'm gonna move your arms and legs,
觉得痛就告诉我  好吗
and you tell me ‭if there's any pain, okay?
-有心电图吗  -什么
- Did we get an EKG? - The what?
各位  我们有心电图吗
Gentlemen, did we get an EKG?
-什么  -他现在接了五导联
- What? - He's on a five-lead now.
还没接十二导联
We didn't get a 12-lead.
-不  -特莉莎  我们需要十二导联
- No. - ‭Okay, Tricia, we're gonna need a 12-lead, please.
不要心电图  不要心电图
No EKG! No EKG!
查尔斯  我们必须做心电图
Yes, Charles, ‭we need to do an EKG okay?
-不  你不懂  -查尔斯
- No, you don't understand. - Charles.
-我有特殊病症  -查尔斯  我们要...
- I have a condition! - Charles, we need --
我有电磁过敏症
I have a hypersensitivity to electricity!
-好  但你必须...  -查尔斯
- Okay, but you need... - Charles,
请你用双脚抵住我的双手
please push your feet against my hands.
-检查你的头部和颈部  -很好
- ...so we examine your head and your neck... - ‭Very good.
确认心脏没问题  好吗
...and make sure your heart's all right, okay?
拿开
Get these out of here.
-不  你不能碰这个  -我有一种病症
- No, you can't touch this. - No, I-I-I have a condition.
-特莉莎  把灯打开  -你们没经我同意
- Tricia, can I get a light? - I did not give you my consent.
-请别触碰  -你们无权这么做
- You can't touch that. - You have no right to do this!
-我们得监测你的心率  -拿开
- We need to monitor your heart, okay? - Get these out of here!
-查尔斯  -放轻松
- Charles. - ‭Just relax.
-请关灯  -放轻松
- The lights, please. - Just relax.
保持冷静  查尔斯
Please stay calm, Charles.
查尔斯  你得配合我们
Charles, you need to cooperate with us.
这非常简单的
This is gonna be very easy.
我们只需要抽一点点血
We're just gonna draw a little bit of blood,
缝合你的伤口  做个简单的断层扫描
suture up your wound, and do a very simple CAT scan.
-不  不能做扫描  -冷静  冷静
- No! No CAT scan! - Okay, c-calm, calm.
-不能做扫描  -特莉莎
- No CAT scan! - Tricia,
请将他固定
can we please get some restraints?
-你不明白  -男医生麻烦进来
- You don't understand! - Gentlemen, please come in here.
求求你  把灯关掉
Please, turn off the lights.
要把他按住
You have to hold him down, restrain him.
-请把灯关掉  -查尔斯
- Please turn off the lights! - Charles...
-这边  -你得冷静
- Right here. - ...we need you to calm down.
-你这是在谋杀我  -冷静  查尔斯
- You're killing me! - Calm down, Charles.
-检查了就没事了  -你没事的
- Just gonna get them and figure it out for you. - You're fine.
有我们在呢
We got you.
头别抬起来
Just keep your head down.
他情况如何
How's he doing?
我也想告诉你
I'd love to be able to tell you,
但是不做检查没办法确定
but we can't know for sure until we do those tests.
你知道我要说什么
You know what I'm gonna say.
你们为什么不能用传统方法
Why can't you just go old-school -- you know,
检查瞳孔  用听诊器之类的
look at his pupils, use a stethoscope -- that kinda thing?
他不想待在这里
He doesn't want to be here.
他想要什么和他需要什么
What he wants and what he needs
完全是两码事  吉米
are two very different things, Jimmy.
我们不知道他失去意识
We don't know if he lost consciousness
是心脏问题还是轻微中风引起的
because of a heart-related issue or if it was a mild stroke.
我们不知道他脊椎是否受伤
We don't know if his spine has been injured,
脑部是否肿胀
if his brain is swelling.
至少很有可能脑震荡
He likely has a concussion, at least.
查克还是拒绝做检查
Chuck is once again refusing these tests
因为会让他受到"电磁轰炸"
because they involve being bombarded by electricity --
这是他的原话
his words.
跟他上次进医院一模一样
Nothing has changed since the last time he was in here.
我已经解释得很清楚了
Look, I don't know ‭how to explain this any clearer.
我不会让他住院的
I'm not committing him.
那申请临时紧急监护人如何
What about a Temporary Emergency Guardianship?
他符合条件
I mean, he fits the parameters.
你跟我说他急需医疗
You're telling me he's in need of medical care so urgent
没办法等到法庭完成审核程序
that we can't wait around on court procedure.
没错
Most certainly.
而且查克无法理解后果
Yeah. And Chuck is not able to understand the consequences.
他是可以理解  但是他...
I mean, he can ‭understand them, but he --
没错
Absolutely.
法官也会这么理解的
A judge will see it that way, too.
之后我带他回家就可以了
And then I take him home, and it's over.
等待检验结果和适当治疗  可以
Pending results and proper treatment, yes.
我认识个法官  现在就可以联系他
I know a judge we can call right now.
让我来告诉他吧
Let me be the one to tell him.
老兄  你还好吗
Hey, buddy. How's it going?
查克
Chuck.
你简直是随时待命
Well, if it isn't Johnny-on-the-spot.
什么意思
What? What does that mean?
欧内斯托在外面吗
Is Ernesto out there?
对  你需要什么吗
Yeah. Can I get you something?
欧内斯托
Ernesto!
麻烦你进来
Come in here, please!
放松
Look, just take it easy.
欧内斯托
Ernesto!
把你东西放那儿
Just put your stuff in there.
来了
I got him.
你感觉怎么样  麦吉尔先生
How are you feelin', Mr. McGill?
欧内斯托  在那家复件店里
Ernesto, ‭how long was I unconscious
我昏迷了多久
in that print shop?
我不确定
I'm not sure.
三十秒  一分钟
30 seconds, a minute?
-还是两分钟  -大概有一分钟吧
- 2 minutes? - ‭I'd say maybe about a minute.
你时而清醒时而迷糊
You were kinda in and out.
救护车来之前我在地上躺了多久
And how long was I lying on the floor before the ambulance arrived?
大概有十分钟吧  我没看表
About 10 minutes, I think, but I didn't look at the clock.
而那时你已经到了
And yet, you were there.
查克  我们能不能...
Chuck, can we, uh...
只有一种方法
There's only one way
能让你那么快到达那里
you could have gotten there so quickly --
你根本没走
you never left.
你太激动了
I think you're getting all wound up.
你得深呼吸...
Can you just take a few deep br--
你贿赂了他...
You bribed him --
-那个柜员  -什么
- that kid behind the counter. - What?
趁着欧内斯托离开而我还没到
Between the time Ernesto left and I arrived,
你给了那个笨蛋钱
you paid that half-wit to swear
-让他说他从没见过你  -麦吉尔先生
- he'd never laid eyes on you. - Mr. McGill.
然后你就在附近一直看着
And then you stuck around to watch.
-为什么  想看我受苦吗  -麦吉尔先生
- Why? Just wanted to see me suffer? - Mr. McGill.
想看我出洋相吗
Just wanted to have a laugh at my expense?
我给他打了电话
I called him.
什么
What?
我在接你之前  给吉米打了电话
I called Jimmy earlier, before I picked you up.
他出现是因为我给他打了电话
He showed up when he did because I called him.
我很担心你  所以...
I was worried about you, and I just --
我给他打了电话  对不起
I called him. I'm sorry.
出去  你们两个都出去
Get out...both of you.
查克  有件事我必须得做
Chuck, there's something that I have to do,
真的很抱歉
and I'm really sorry --
真的非常抱歉
really, truly sorry,
但我必须做  为了你好
but I gotta do it, and it's for you.
你想让我住院
You're trying to have me committed.
不  只是临时...
No, it's a Temporary --
临时紧急监护人
Temporary ‭Emergency Guardianship --
说法不同而已
to-may-to, to-mah-to.
你终于把我关起来了
Well, you've finally got me where you want me.
你看起来累坏了
Hey, you look beat.
回家休息吧
Why don't you go home and get some sleep?
我还撑得住
I'm fine to hang out, you know?
有什么需要尽管说
Whatever you need.
没事  不用了
Nah. We're good here.
欧尼
Hey, Ernie.
你为什么说你给我打了电话
Uh, how come you said that about callin' me?
我也不知道
I don't know, man.
我本不想多嘴
Look, I didn't want to say anything,
但是你哥哥...
but your brother --
最近他说起你时的样子...
the way he's been ‭talkin' about you lately --
就好像...他真的要收拾你  吉米
it's like...he's really out to get you, Jimmy.
我说不清
And...I don't know.
你是我的朋友
You're my friend.
谢谢
Thanks.
我明天给你电话
I'll call you tomorrow.
真怀念收发室
I miss the mailroom.
你们知道希波克拉底誓言吗
Are you familiar with the Hippocratic oath?
你们应该知道
You should be.
历史上最古老的具有约束力的文件之一
One of the oldest binding documents in history.
首先  不要伤害病人
Primum non nocere -- first, do no harm.
你们这样治疗我是不对的
This is not the way to treat my condition.
就好像  我对青霉素过敏
It's as though I had a -- an allergy to penicillin,
而你们却非要用它来治疗我的感染
and yet, you persist on treating my infection with it.
感谢你做类比  查尔斯
I appreciate the analogy, Charles,
但我觉得这个类比并不恰当
but I don't think it quite fits.
我们会在你不知不觉间
Look, we'll have you in and out of Radiology
就做完放射检查的  好吗
before you know it, all right?
然后我们会摘掉颈托
Then we can see about getting that neck collar off
让你活动活动
and get you moving around.
好了  查尔斯  扫描就要开始了
Okay, Charles, the scan is starting now.
你躺着的台子会移动
The table that you're on is going to move.
你会听到一声比较大的声响
You're gonna hear a sound that might seem loud to you,
但是不用担心
but it's nothing to worry about.
还没消息呢
Still no word?
天啊
Jesus.
到底要花多久啊
How long is this gonna take?
她说整个检查也就十分钟而已
She said that whole test would be like 10 minutes.
也许他们得重做
Maybe they had to start over.
重做二十次吗
What -- 20 times?
他应该回家
He should be home.
吉米  你这么做是对的
Jimmy, you're doin' the right thing.
你能把工作拿出来做吗
Would you get your work out, please?
因为不知道还要在这等多久
Becouse God knows how much longer we're gonna be here.
如果你能做点别的我会感觉好点
I'd feel better ‭if you were doing something,
做点跟医院无关的事
you know, unhospital-y.
跟医院无关的
Unhospital-y.
好的
I'm on it.
我去问一下情况
You know what? I'm gonna go ask for an update.
好主意
Okay. Good idea.
你们是最伟大的一代
You are the greatest generation.
-吉米  -你们没有挑起二战
- Jimmy. ‭- You didn't start World War II,
但却终结了它
but you sure as heck finished it.
如果这还不够
And if that weren't enough,
你们还把九十多米高的火箭送上了月球
you sent a rocket 300 feet tall to the moon.
现在  你们到了迟暮之年
Now, in your golden years,
需要有人照顾
you need someone looking out for you,
需要一个可以信任的人
someone you can trust,
一个言必信  行必果的人
a man who says what he does and does what he says.
当你需要一个可靠的人
When you need someone to count on...
-我选吉米  -我选吉米
- Gimme Jimmy! - Gimme Jimmy!
我选吉米
Gimme Jimmy!
因为现在勇气已经很少见了
Because moxie is in such short supply these days.
吉米·麦吉尔  你可以信赖的律师
Jimmy McGill -- A lawyer you can trust.
太棒了  吉米
It's really good, Jimmy.
你拍了一条很棒的广告
You made a really good commercial.
谢了
Thanks.
吉米
Jimmy.
总算出来了  他怎么样了
Oh, finally. So, how is he?
好消息是生理上无大碍
Well, the good news is that, physically, he's okay.
放射科医生说查尔斯的
The radiologist said everything looks normal
头和脊椎都很正常
with Charles' head and spine,
所以我们把他的颈圈卸了
so we took his neck collar off.
他头部的伤会很快愈合
His head wound will heal just fine.
给他打了破伤风
We gave him a tetanus shot
因为他的接种记录不是最新的
because his immunization records were not current.
你肯定不意外
I'm sure ‭that's no surprise to you.
那他心脏呢
And -- And -- And his heart?
很强健
Strong.
心电图正常
The EKG was normal.
至于失去知觉  最可能的原因是
As far as losing consciousness, my best guess is
查尔斯的晕厥和压力有关
Charles had what's called a stress-related syncope.
一般是恐慌症发作
It's basically a panic attack,
但没有中风和心脏问题
but no signs of a stroke or cardiac event.
但还是有...
However, there was...
并发症
a complication.
查克  兄弟是我
Chuck? Hey, buddy, it's me.
医生说一切正常  我们出院吧
They said everything looks good, so let's get you outta here.
你说呢
Whaddya say?
他怎么了
What's wrong with him?
药效应该已经过去了  对吧
Whatever you gave him should've worn off already, right?
我们观察他几个小时了
We watched him for several hours.
甚至都用了逆转剂
We even gave him ‭what's called a reversal agent.
没错  镇静剂药效过了
So, yes, the sedative wore off.
-是因为其他原因  -什么原因
- This is something else. ‭- What?
我们认为这是自诱导紧张症
We think it's a state of self-induced catatonia.
"我们"  永远是"我们认为"
"We" -- always with the "We."
我觉得就是你认为
I think it's you.
你是这屋子里唯一的医生
You're the only doctor in the room.
我认为是你用机器烧坏了他的脑子
I think you fried his brain with that machine.
吉米
Jimmy.
-抱歉  真是扯淡  -吉米
- I'm sorry. This is bullshit. - Jimmy.
接下来干嘛
What next?
我第一次治疗查尔斯时  他也是类似的状态
When I first treated Charles, he was in a similar state.
你同意吗
Wouldn't you agree?
我相信他清醒过来
I have to believe ‭that it's just a matter of time
只是时间问题
before he comes out of it.
时间问题
Matter of time.
好  那我就在这等着
Fine, then. I'll wait right here.
偏左  一点五角分
Shot left. 1.5 minutes.
这把枪能连射多少发
How many rounds've gone through the tube?
你说鲁格762狙击枪吗
For a 762?
就算射掉3500发也没啥影响
You can put 3,500 through it and never know.
关键是能射多准
It's about how tight she shoots.
这把枪准得很
And this one's tight as they come.
因为顺射击方向有风
I'd say there's a breeze picking up downrange.
枪管会变冷吗
Your barrel gonna be cold?
希望如此吧
Let's suppose so.
那你开枪最好多留心
Well, then, you'd better have paid attention to that shot.
是啊
I'd better have.
向右调整  一点五角分
Adjusting right, 1.5 minutes.
开枪吧
Send it.
中了
Hit.
正中红心
Center hit.
我建议你不要换子弹
I suggest you don't change up your ammo.
继续用168格令船尾中空弹
Stick with the 168 grain boat-tail hollow point --
如果没有障碍物  选它没错
if it's an open shot, that is.
如果你要射穿很厚的窗户
Now, if you got to shoot through a heavy window,
我建议你换到180格令
I'll up you to a 180.
但你就得重新计算射击参数了
But as you know, you'll have to recalculate the shot.
168就够了
168'll do it.
多少盒
How many boxes?
就一盒
Just the one.
不用了  免费
No, it's on the house.
还有一件事
Uh, one last thing.
无意冒犯
No offense.
没事
None taken.
吉米  可以给我点水吗
Jimmy, can I get some water?
查克  你醒了
Chuck. Hey, buddy, you're back with us.
你怎么...
How you...
可以给我点水吗
Can I get some water, please?
好好  我去拿
Yeah, yeah, water.
该死  抱歉
Oh, shit. Sorry. ‭
还要吗
Want some more?
我记得最后一件事
Last thing I remember
就是他们把我送进那台机器里
was that machine they put me in.
我昏迷多久了
How long was I out for?
有二十个小时了
Was...20 hours.
下一个任务就是把你带出这鬼地方
And next order of business -- get you the hell outta here.
去哪
Where to next --
拉斯克鲁塞斯的精神病院吗
some insane asylum in Las Cruces?
一个你可以真正把我藏起来的地方吗
Some place you can really tuck me away, but good?
回家  查克  你要回家
Home, Chuck. You're goin' home.
你心脏很好
Well, your heart's okay,
头上的伤也没事
and so is that crack on your head,
这已经很好了
so that's all I wanted to know.
临时紧急监护人呢
What about the T.E.G.?
"T"不正是临时的意思吗
The "T" stands for "Temporary," Right?
你想上床吗
You wanna go to bed?
不不  这更凉快
No, no. ‭It's -- It's cooler down here.
你还需要什么
What can I get you?
我给你泡点茶  好茶叶
I'll make you some tea -- uh, the good stuff,
不是医院里那种发黄的水
not that brown water they have at the hospital.
不用了
I'm fine.
我去给你泡茶
I'll make you some tea.
吉米  别去
Jimmy. No.
你就...
Just --
你没事了
You've done your duty.
你可以走了
You can go now.
我有点咄咄逼人了
That came out a bit harsh.
我在医院已经被百般折磨了
Look, I've been zapped and poked and prodded,
现在  我只想自己待会
and now I just I wanna be left alone.
如果你身体又出什么问题
If things start going south for you again,
我怎么能知道呢
how am I even gonna know?
我没事的  我保证
I'm fine. I promise.
看见没
See?
已经感觉好多了
Feeling better already.
我连钥匙都没有
I mean, ‭I don't even have a key, so...
我能叫欧尼回来吗
Can I get Ernie back here?
至少让我为你做这件事  行吗
Would you let me ‭do that for you, at least?
你需要有人来照看你
You need someone lookin' in on ya.
你得吃饭  不是吗
You gotta eat, right?
好吧
All right.
早日康复  查克
Feel better, Chuck.
别这么做
好的  我这就去办
All right, I will get right on that.
下周应该就能帮你办好
I should have it for you by early next week.
祝你今日愉快  柯林斯先生
You have yourself ‭a wonderful day, Mr. Collins.
对了
Oh! There you go.
把墨镜拿出来
Yeah, get the sunglasses out.
外面很亮
It's very bright.
得保护好眼睛
Gotta protect the ol' peepers.
你得...
You gotta...
好  帅呆了
Yep, looking sharp.
就这样
Bingo.
回头见
Uh, bye-bye, now.
好了
Okay.
大家好  抱歉让你们久等
Folks, I'm sorry about the wait,
我为每位委托人花这么长时间
but the attention I give each client means
意味着有时候大家需要等等
sometimes, things get a little...backed up.
不过我向你们保证
Uh but I promise
会按顺序为你们服务
to get to each and every one of you in turn.
德谢佐女士  亲爱的  你是下一位
Mrs. DeShazo, my dear, I believe you're next.
先问一句  有谁想喝咖啡吗
But first, may I get anybody some coffee?
我能和你谈谈吗
Can I talk to you?
稍等一下
Uh, excuse me one second.
我们昨天就得找个前台
We have got to get a receptionist -- like, yesterday.
吉米  霍华德刚才来电话了
Jimmy, Howard just called.
他说他一早上都在联系你
He says he's been trying to reach you all morning.
那又怎样  叫他别烦你了  给我留言
So? Tell him to stop bothering you and leave me a message.
是查克的事
It's about Chuck.
他只说很重要
It's impmptant -- that's all he'll say.
好吧
Okay.
很遗憾  我的同事告诉我
Unfortunately, uh, my associate tells me
我有简短但紧急的法律事务要处理
I'm needed for some brief but pressing legal business.
我很快打个电话就好
I just need to make one quick phone call.
谁想要咖啡来着
Uh, in the meantime, who was it who wanted coffee?
好的  这位年轻的女士会给你们倒咖啡
Yeah, okay, uh, this young lady will get you coffee...
还有面包圈  如果还有的话
and, also, doughnuts if there are any left.
我要咖啡  不加奶
I want coffee, but I do not want cream.
朱莉  是我  给霍华德回电话
Hey, Julie, it's me, returning Howard's call.
对
Yeah.
怎么了
Hey, what's up?
吉米  我就问一个问题
Jimmy, ‭I have just one question --
这是你策划的吗
are you behind this?
策划什么
Am I behind what?
吉米  我现在正忙着呢
Jimmy, I'm kind of in the middle of somethin' right now.
-过会再来吧  -不  不  不
- Come back later. - No, no, no.
拜托  把门打开
Come on. Open the door.
我知道你为什么来  我们可以一会再说
I know why you're here. We can discuss it later.
我正忙着呢  再见
Right now I'm busy, goodbye.
满意了吧
You happy now?
这样不行  我连这里的钥匙都没有
It's not right -- me not havin' a key to this place.
查克
Chuck?
查克  这怎么回事
So, Chuck...uh, what's up?
你弄了个...
You got a little, uh --
你弄了个工程啊
You got a little, uh, uh, project goin' on?
你想跟我说说这是怎么回事吗
Uh, something you maybe wanna tell me about?
查克  跟我说说行吗
Whaddya say, Chuck? Y-- Uh, clue me in?
这些墙是石膏和板条的
These walls are plaster and lath --
对无线电波完全没防护作用
completely invisible to the radio spectrum.
一点也没有
No protection at all --
我还不如直接站到一片牧草地里呢
I might as well be standing in the middle of a pasture.
真不知道当初怎么想的
I don't know what I was thinking.
一开始就该这么做
Shoulda done this from the start.
你是说这么做  用...
What, you shoulda done this, with the, uh --
我觉得这些墙还挺结实的
See, I think these walls are pretty solid. I think --
一种金属材质外壳  能阻止电磁波进入
我需要的是一个法拉第笼
See, what I really need is a proper Faraday cage.
那才是我需要的
That's what I need.
我们该坐下来  休息一会  伙计
I think we need to sit down, take a break, buddy.
求你了
Please?
别跟我来这一套  吉米
Do not patronize me, Jimmy.
我没疯  好吗
I'm not crazy, all right?
我从没说你疯了
‭I-I never said you were crazy.
你可能只是累坏了
That -- You're probably exhausted,
情有可原
a-and justifiably.
听着
Hey, come on. Hey.
就五分钟  然后你接着忙你的
Five minutes, and then right back at it.
我没事
I'm fine.
来吧  查克
Come on, Chuck.
休息一会
Just a break.
-小心点  -我知道
- Careful. - ‭I know.
霍华德说你辞职了
Howard tells me you quit HHM.
我没有辞职
I didn't quit.
我退休了
I retired.
听起来可不像退休
That's not what it sounded like.
不管怎样  这太突然了  你不觉得吗
Regardless, it's kinda outta the blue, don't you think?
他很担心你
He's worried about you.
他该松了一口气才对
He should be relieved.
松了一口气  怎么会
Relieved? Why would he be relieved?
你可是他的顶梁柱
You're his Number One Guy.
没了你  律所肯定每况愈下
Without you, that whole place goes down the drain.
你退休了
So, you -- you retired --
不仅从哈姆林麦吉尔联合律所退休
not just from HHM,
也退出律师界了吗
but the law?
这可不好  查克
That's not good, Chuck.
律师界  需要你
The -- The law... needs you.
别说了
Just stop it.
你也需要它
And you need it.
到底是为什么  查克
What brought this on exactly, Chuck?
你不做律师还能做什么
'Cause I don't know what you are if you're not a lawyer.
你还没让我被取消律师资格
How are you gonna retire before you get me disbarred,
还没把我赶出城  怎么能退休
before you run me outta town on a rail, huh?
以后可就我一个麦吉尔在律师界混了
I'll be the only McGill carrying the family name.
你怎么忍得了
You can't have that.
是因为  你没能挽回梅萨维德银行吗
Is this... ‭'cause you lost Mesa Verde?
那又怎样  谁会在意
So what? Who cares?
而且  如果你真的觉得
And, hey, if you truly do think
这事是我在背后捅你刀子
that I rat-fucked you on that thing --
当然我并没有  不过随便了
which I did not, but whatever --
你知道吗
well, you know what?
你应该生气  应该报复
You get mad! Take action!
别躲在你这法拉第什么
Don't just hide out in your -- your Faraday whatever --
破笼子里
your cage thing here.
不  你该永不退休才对
No! You -- No retirement for you!
等你九十九岁了
When you're 99,
还要对着机器人法官做结辩陈词  然后倒地身亡
you can drop dead giving closing arguments to JudgeBot 3000 --
对了  那东西也是用电的
which will run on electricity, by the way.
这才是你的未来好吗
That's your future, okay?
-所以  -我
- So... ‭ - I...
我做不了这个工作了
‭I can't do the job anymore.
什么意思  你怎么就干不了了
What do you mean? ‭'Course you can do the job.
我犯了一个错误
I made a mistake.
什么错误
What mistake?
一个很小的错误  把银行地址搞错了
A simple, ‭nothing little bank address --
1261号写成了1216号
1216 instead of 1261.
我搞砸了
I screwed it up!
我让委托人蒙受损失
I hurt the client.
彻彻底底搞砸了
Blew it completely and utterly.
而且我还把这怪到你头上
And then I blamed -- And then I blamed you.
都怪这该死的电流
It's this goddamned electricity!
一点一点消磨我  把我的机能消磨殆尽
It's wearing me down! It's wearing down my faculties!
我的头脑  我的思维  曾经
My brain...my mind -- it used to be --
它曾经那么敏捷
You know, it used to work!
可现在完全不管用了
And now it doesn't anymore.
有人因为我而受伤害
People got hurt because of me.
是时候结束了
Time to end it.
如果我告诉你你并没有犯错呢
What if I told you ‭you didn't make a mistake?
天哪  吉米  别来安慰我了
For Christ's sakes, Jimmy, stop humoring me.
别说得好像一切都不是我的错
Stop trying to talk everything right.
我背叛了你
I rat-fucked you.
是我干的
It was me.
尼克松都得为我自豪
I would made Nixon proud.
我把1261改成了1216
I changed 1261 to 1216.
是我干的
It was me.
事情的经过就像你说的一样
It all went down exactly like you said --
分毫不差
I mean, exactly.
我篡改了文件
I doctored the copies.
买通打印店的小伙子让他为我撒谎
I paid the kid at the shop to lie for me.
每一个细节都如你所料  你太神了
It is insane how you got every detail exactly right.
这下你能放心了吧
So you can relax, okay?
你的脑子好用着呢  马力十足
'Cause that brain of yours is chugging along at 1,000% efficiency.
你说的是真的吗
Are you telling the truth,
还是你只是为了让我好受点
or are you just trying to make me feel better?
当然是为了让你好受点
I am sayin' it to make ya feel better.
不然我怎么可能说出来
I sure as shit wouldn't be telling ya otherwise.
但没错  这就是真相
But, yes... it's the truth.
你这么大费周章就为了羞辱我吗
You'd go to such lengths to humiliate me?
我是为了金
I did it for Kim!
她废寝忘食拿下梅萨维德银行
What -- She worked her butt off to get Mesa Verde
而你和霍华德就喝喝威士忌坐享其成
while you and Howard sat around sipping Scotch and chortling.
什么哈姆林麦吉尔联合律所
Hamlin, Hamlin, McGill --
应该叫斯克鲁奇马利律所才对
more like Scrooge and Marley!
狄更斯小说中的守财奴
梅萨维德银行是金的
Kim deserves Mesa Verde --
不是你  也不是哈姆林麦吉尔联合律所的not you, not HHM.
她争取来的  她需要它
She earned it, and she needs it!
我这么做是为了帮她
I did it to help her,
但我真不知道这会给你带来那么大的伤害
but I-I honestly didn't think it would hurt you so bad.
我以为你只会说  "靠  我犯了个错误"
I thought you'd just say, "Oh, crap, I made a mistake,"
然后继续过你的日子  这才是正常人会干的
and go on with your life, like a normal person!
可你偏不
But, oh, no!
是我太天真
Wishful thinking!
所以  我能不能告诉霍华德
So, can I, uh, tell Howard
你不辞职也不退休了
you're not quitting or retiring or whatever?
还有  能不能把这些破玩意从墙上弄下来
And can we take all this shit down off the walls?
我这就打电话给霍华德
I'm gonna go call Howard.
吉米
Jimmy.
你刚刚承认犯了一项重罪你知道吧
You do realize ‭you just confessed to a felony?
算是吧
I guess.
可你觉得好多了  是吧
But you feel better, right?
再说了  就我们俩  空口无凭
Besides, ‭it's your word against mine.